There's so many friends, I've never had a baby like you, I've never signed up for them.
I'm Kroos Pedrone and I'm part of the graduating advertising class of the best year ever 2020.
Currently I'm living it up in Nashville. I work at this really really cool agency called GSNF.
I am an account executive in the interactive department which is basically me being a project manager with a bunch of web developers, app developers, all that stuff.
And I get the absolute pleasure of doing sometimes what we call a smoke screen client.
Kidding, kind of.
You might be asking yourself, cool, Kroos, what do you do on the day to day?
Well, I'd probably have a different response for you depending on the day you ask me.
My days can be full of meetings, coming up with briefs which are super fun.
Taking clients out to fancy lunches to talk to this, to even just working directly with the CEO of the company on a passion project of theirs.
And it is super interesting, super dynamic.
You can never guess what's going to happen tomorrow.
I mean the best you can do is try to set your calendar so that people don't have meetings to do that so that doesn't work.
When I think back on my days studying advertising at UT, some of the best aspects was just realizing how broad advertising is.
It's not just a typical TV or radio ads.
It goes beyond that.
The psychology aspect really interested me.
Everything that encompasses it was so intriguing and it was really really cool.
And I felt that I was really learning some awesome stuff.
I could be taking one course and then the next course you take is completely unrelated.
But it doesn't connect until you're at the end of it all.
And you're like, wow, this is pretty cool.
And also it was really cool to do group projects and figure out which one of my group members was brave enough to get sushi from a partner.
Which I don't know if that's still around.
I think working and advertising is really cool.
It's a pure part of this club of just seeing how things will work on the inside in terms of marketing and all that.
When you're on the other side of it, you see all the decisions that go into making it good or bad commercial.
And it's kind of cool.
It's really cool.
I also remember being in pretty much the same shoes a lot of yours right now.
I could not have imagined what I'm at right now back then.
But it just kind of goes to show just how crazy life can be and how much you can grow in life.
Something that's really awesome about the industry, you know, is you're going to be a lot of people that have the same mindset.
It doesn't matter whether background, they'll have kind of this energy about them.
And that's really cool.
That's something that you kind of start noticing in people.
I just kind of wanted to give you a little alumni check-in.
Who knows?
Maybe it's going to be you doing this video in a couple of years and putting on your own spin to it.
You're all going to have so much fun.
It's going to be a crazy little while ride.
If you stick with advertising, it's going to be worth it in the end.
I wish you all the best luck starting out this semester.
And, you know, if you guys have any questions, if you want to connect through LinkedIn or email,
hit up Dr. Chillier's for that information.
I'll be more than happy to get back to you all.
But most importantly, go Vols.